newsciti.com 2018-05-11

# Privacy Policies › NewsCiti.com : Submit Article, URL Submission of High PR Bookmarking Sites | Social Bookmark Manager, Add Web Sites To Your Personal Collection of Links, Categorize With Tags & Share It

We are committed to protecting your privacy. We will only collect and use information about you lawfully and in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998.

**Personal Information Collection:**  
We collect only your name, e-mail address, submitted stories and profile data. We care about the information we collect and it is used for helping you with the best possible services. We only collect personal information that is relevant to the purpose of our website, which is to enable users to discover and share information with one another. This information allows us to provide you with a customized and efficient experience. We do not process this information in a way that is incompatible with this objective. We receive and store any information you enter on our website or provide to us in any other way. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features.

**Protection of Personal Information:**  
Your account information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. Protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer by logging off once you have finished using a shared computer. As stated previously, you can always opt not to disclose information, but then you may be unable to use certain features on our website, such as posting new links. By visiting your User Profile, you can correct, amend, add or delete personal information on our website. When you update information, however, we often maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records. You may request deletion of your account by visiting contact us page and sending email with detailed information. Please note that you will continue to receive all system e-mails (e.g. those regarding forgotten user passwords) and legal notices (e.g. updates to our policies) from us.

We never share sensitive information about you without your explicit consent. We do not sell or pass any user's personal information, e-mail addresses included, to any other organization for any purpose. The information is held under high security and would not be shared for any reasons whatsoever. Information will not be kept for longer than is necessary. The information we hold will be accurate and wherever necessary, kept up to date. You can check the information we hold about you, by contacting us via e-mail. We will immediately correct any errors you find. Data held about you will be done so under extreme.

**Registration:**  
In order for you to use website services, such as submitting new links to the website, you must complete a registration form. As part of this registration form, we require select personal information (including your full name, city, state and e-mail address).

**User Profile:**  
To allow you to express yourself beyond just the information collected during registration, we enable you to provide additional information, such as a bio, favorite URLs, and instant messaging IDs. In addition, you may choose to include photos of yourself in your profile. You can control how your information is displayed and used. We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. We are authorized to receive and record certain "traffic data" on their server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information, and the page you requested. We uses this traffic data to help diagnose problems with its servers, analyze trends and administer the website. We may collect and, on any page, display the total counts that page has been viewed.

**Links to Other Sites :**  
The website contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such websites. Inclusion of links to an outside website, whether in an advertisement or content area of the website, is not an endorsement of the website or a guarantee that the information it contains is accurate.

**Cookies:**  
Cookies are text files stored on your computer when you visit web pages on our web site. This site uses cookies to improve your visit and to display relevant ads to you on third party web sites. Your privacy is important to us, you should also know how browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. Please note, however, that if your browser does not accept cookies, you will not be able to take advantage of some of our attractive features. The data contained in the cookie used for third party advertising is completely anonymous and does not contain any of your personal details. We would like to continue showing relevant ads to you, but if you would prefer to opt-out of this service. To do so, please visit http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

**Children Under 18 Years of Age:**  
You must be 13 years and older to register to use the website. As a result our site does not specifically collect information about children. If we learn that collected information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. We recommend that minors between the ages of 13 and 18 ask and receive their parents' permission before using site or sending information about themselves or anyone else over the Internet. We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, at its sole discretion. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes to the Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the website so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances if any, it is disclosed.

**Conditions of Use:**  
If you decide to visit our website, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of country law.
